phoneaddressdirectory.com 2014-05-24

# Privacy Policy | Phone Address Directory

Phone Address Directory provides the website PhoneAddressDirectory.com to you ("You" or "Your") subject to this Privacy Policy, its Terms of Service, and its other policies. 

This Privacy Policy describes the way in which Phone Address Directory collects, uses, or shares any information You provide to PhoneAddressDirectory.com or information about Your use of PhoneAddressDirectory.com ("Personal Information").

Phone Address Directory may change this Privacy Policy at any time. The most current version of this policy can be accessed at  http://www.phoneaddressdirectory.com/privacy.html.  By continuing to access or use PhoneAddressDirectory.com, You accept any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy.

**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY DO NOT USE PhoneAddressDirectory.com**

**1.     Information Available Through PhoneAddressDirectory.com Phone Search**

a)    Phone Address Directory aggregates publicly available information from phone books, cellular networks, marketing surveys, real estate listings, business websites, and other public sources ("Public Information").  This Public Information may be made available to users through the PhoneAddressDirectory.com people and phone search.  Phone Address Directory does not verify and cannot guarantee the accuracy of this Public Information.

b)    Personal Information, such as information that You provide to PhoneAddressDirectory.com or information about Your use of PhoneAddressDirectory.com is not part of the Public Information available to users through the PhoneAddressDirectory.com people & phone search.

**2.     Personal Information Phone Address Directory Collects**

a)    You may use PhoneAddressDirectory.com without creating an account.  Even without an account, Phone Address Directory collects information about Your use of PhoneAddressDirectory.com.  This may include information about any IP address used to access PhoneAddressDirectory.com and Your activity on PhoneAddressDirectory.com.  PhoneAddressDirectory.com uses cookies, or small text files stored on Your computer, to store data about Your visits.

b)    Phone Address Directory collects information that You provide in creating an account at PhoneAddressDirectory.com. This may include information such as Your name, email address, or phone number.

  c)    Certain features of PhoneAddressDirectory.com permit You to enter personal information to access Your accounts with third-party websites.  In some instances, this information is not stored by Phone Address Directory.  For example, You may choose to provide Your email account login credentials to import Your address book contacts into PhoneAddressDirectory.com.   Your email account login credentials will only be used for the one-time address book import and will not be stored.

d)    Other features of PhoneAddressDirectory.com must store Your third-party login credentials to function.  For example, You may choose to provide Your third-party login credentials to syndicate private content from third-party social networks and websites.  Under these circumstances, Your third-party login credentials will be stored only so long as You continue to enable private content syndication from these third-party social networks and websites.  Should You terminate Your use of the syndication tool, this information will be deleted within a reasonable period of time following the termination.  Your third-party login credentials are hashed and stored with the strictest security standards.

**3.     Use and Sharing of Personal Information**

a)    Phone Address Directory may use Personal Information You provide to PhoneAddressDirectory.com to create and maintain Your account, to personalize Your experience, and to send periodic email communications relating to our services, such as purchase receipts, and account confirmations.  Phone Address Directory does not sell, exchange, transfer, or give this type of Personal Information to any other company without Your consent.

b)    Phone Address Directory may use Personal Information about Your use of PhoneAddressDirectory.com to improve our services.  Phone Address Directory actively protects Your usage anonymity and does not distribute personally identifiable information about Your use of PhoneAddressDirectory.com to any third parties. Only aggregated use data that does not include personally identifiable information may be shared with third parties. 

c)    Phone Address Directory reserves the right to disclose Personal Information to third parties if required to do so by law, or if Phone Address Directory has a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; (3) act in an emergency to protect someone’s safety.

d)    Phone Address Directory reserves the right to transfer Personal Information to any successor in interest to the Phone Address Directory business.

e)    The Privacy Policy describes Phone Address Directory’s handling of personally identifiable information as required by the California Online Privacy Protection Act.

**4.     Children’s Privacy**

a)    PhoneAddressDirectory.com is directed to people who are at least 18 years old, and Phone Address Directory does not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18.  If You are aware that Phone Address Directory has collected Personal Information from someone under the age of 18, please alert Phone Address Directory at support@phoneaddressdirectory.com and the information will be removed from our system as soon as is reasonably possible. This policy regarding collection of data from children exceeds the requirements of the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act.

b)    Phone Address Directory does not knowingly aggregate or provide Public Information about people under the age of 18.  Phone Address Directory’s email search may return Public Information about children between the ages of 13 and 18 because this Public Information originates from third-party social networking sites and websites that permit children who are 13 years and older to create public profiles.

  **5.     Contacting Phone Address Directory**

a)    If You have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at support@phoneaddressdirectory.com.
